

 \times

peterhoxuandung@outlook.com

+84 943 417821

9

Ho Chi Minh, Viet Nam

peterho249.github.io

in

linkedin.com/in/hoxuandung



+84943417821

0

github.com/PeterHo249

SKILLS

Flutter

Swift 4

Firebase

JavaScript

NodeJS

HTML

CSS

MongoDB

MySQL





INTERESTS

Reading books

Listening to music

Traveling

Dung Xuan Ho

Mobile Developer

Highly responsibility, willingness to learn new things, independent working and positive teamwork attitudes. With the knowledge and skills which I learnt in university and the experience of Flutter, Swift, I want to become part of your mobile development team to create products together.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Software Engineering HCMVNU - University of Science

09/2015 – 05/2019 GPA: 7.96

EXPERIENCE

Fast Store - Freelance project (04/2019 - 05/2019)

- Built front-end for department store.
- Using Firebase to push notification.
- Tech stack: Flutter, Firebase Cloud Function and Cloud Messaging.

Success Hunter - Thesis project (09/2018 – 04/2019)

- Developed an application to support self development process using Gamification method.
- Tech stack: Flutter, Firebase service (Firestore, Cloud Function, Cloud Messaging, Cloud Pub/sub).
- Apple App Store: itunes.apple.com/us/app/success-hunter/id1451431732?mt=8.
- Google Play Store: play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.hoxuandung.successhunter.

Kanbanize - Course project (04/2018 - 07/2018)

- Developed an application to manage todo list with Kanban method on iOS.
- Tech stack: Swift 4, Core Data.
- Repository: github.com/PeterHo249/KANBANize.

Rex Shop - Course project (04/2018 - 07/2018)

- Built a camera and accessory shop website.
- □ Tech stack: Expressjs with HandlebarsJS, MongoDB.
- Repository: github.com/PeterHo249/rexshop.

Yame Shop - Course Project (04/2018 – 07/2018)

- Developed a cloth shop website with pure NodeJS and xml file.
- Tech stack: NodeJS, xml data file.
- Repository: github.com/PeterHo249/yameshop.

Quick Note - Course Project (12/2017 – 01/2018)

- Developed a note tool for Windows, using hotkey to add note. It's written in C/C++ and Win32 API.
- □ Tech stack: C/C++, Win32 API.
- Repository: github.com/PeterHo249/quicknote.

Five in a Row game - Course Project (12/2016 – 01/2017)

- Developed five in a row game can be play on console screen. It provide 2 play mode: person-vs-person and person-vs-computer.
- □ Tech stack: C/C++.
- Repository: github.com/PeterHo249/five in a row.